hey what's up everybody Jeremy Krakowski
here welcome to the grow Your Life
podcast I'm so thankful that you're here
to join us this is for coaches mentors
trainers and thought leaders who want to
scale their businesses and make multiple
six figures online we provide you with
strategies mindset everything that you
need to be able to accomplish this
listen if you haven't yet been a part of
one of our live events that we do check
us out on my social media on Facebook
and Instagram or Twitter and register
for one of the next upcoming events that
we're doing
my mission is to help create over a
thousand millionaire coaches and that
starts by helping you make a hundred
thousand two hundred thousand five
hundred thousand seven hundred and fifty
thousand dollars a million dollars in
your coaching business step by step and
no matter where you're at no matter
where you're coming from
we have resources and trainings to help
you do so and they don't cost anything
either which is awesome we have so much
available to you that there's no reason
that if you're connected with us that
you should ever struggle to scale your
business to make seven figures at all
that's my mission is to help you make
more money than you ever thought was
possible now today I'm going to be
talking about something that hey it's
going to challenge you it's a little bit
controversial but I firmly
believe in this is that I think one of
the greatest reasons why most coaches
mentors and trainers
struggle to make the kind of money they
want to make is their desire to do
everything right
is this this desire to have excellence
and their desire to do everything right
and have Excellence is actually the very
thing that keeps them from making the
kind of money they want to make often
they're so concerned with
people being disappointed
people not liking what they put out
there people being upset that they're
emailing them too often people you know
being upset that something was said a
certain way that maybe alienated a
certain segment of the market all of
these things I find
ultimately stem from being concerned
with how other people perceive us
how they will judge us
and the opinions that other people have
about us and we end up believing that in
order to make the kind of money that we
want to make in our business we have to
please everybody we have to make
everybody happy by doing all the right
thing and often this comes from
whether it be your family of origin
parents how you grew up or the
environment that you're in and it's
usually those two things or maybe an
environment that you've recently left
like a certain corporate job or
something like that
we end up getting trained that if I can
do all the right things
then I will be successful and this
thinking is
flawed
and
by me even saying that it's going to be
challenging a paradigm that you might
have about business
the truth is this is that
because
business is so nuanced
that if it was possible to
prescriptionize doing all the right
things we would have way more
millionaires because people would just
be
following the steps and there's a
fantasy belief that successful people
you might even think this about me hold
back
the keys to the kingdom of what it takes
to be successful
I'll tell you this straight off the bat
there's a lot of great coaches a lot of
great mentors a lot of great
people out there that teach amazing
things there's a lot of crappy ones too
of course but the ones that teach really
good stuff they're not holding back
it's that most people are hearing the
message through the lens of their
beliefs and their experience and they're
filtering it it comes in their ears or
their eyes right because those are how
we receive information
we read it
or we listen to it okay you're listening
to this podcast right now maybe you're
watching the video of it and so we
receive information through our ears or
our eyes and we filter it through
our 30 40 50 years of experience and
oftentimes what goes in
doesn't come out exactly the same way
and so what what I often find happiness
and and this is from me working with
thousands of coaches trainers and
mentors is they tell me Jeremiah I'm
doing all the right things and nothing
is happening successfully
and then when I started asking them what
they're doing it's
legitimately
all the wrong things but according to
how they perceived it it was all the
right things and and and and and sadly
uh most of the time it's it's not as
simple as me just telling them all the
right things to do because they will end
up filtering it the exact same way they
have from everybody else and so I can
literally give them all the right things
and they will end up maybe adjusting a
few things but
there's always like a limiter and a line
that people aren't willing to cross
and this line that people have that
they're not willing to cross with their
actions is what prevents them from being
successful financially now don't take
this to the extreme
I'm not encouraging you to uh you know
do anything immoral or illegal when I
say crossing a line what I'm saying is
as often it's like what we're
comfortable doing or what we have a
habit of doing and that it my friends is
where the rub is
is oftentimes what we have a habit or
what we're comfortable doing is outside
of the realm of what it actually takes
to be successful but in our mind we're
doing all the right things because it's
based on the experience of the years of
our life that we've spent and so we
translate x y z into
all the right things okay it's like a
math equation but but the brain is the
filter okay
and so what ends up happening is over
time because it does actually take time
I I've seen it
so often I'll meet somebody a year ago
and they'll be like
struggling to translate what they need
to do and they finally get it like a
year or two later and it's like and then
they start to see the success or they
take five years or ten years to do this
you know I remember I had a client you
know she's on year seven in her business
and that's when she finally started
making six figures the six years up to
that she wasn't making very much at all
now we can judge the coach and say oh
that coach was bad that they had her
that coach failed them or that coach
didn't do very well and we can point
fingers but all that is is just blaming
outside circumstances for why we aren't
where we want to be now oftentimes I
have found a lot of coaches don't
understand where people are coming from
they might not have empathy for certain
situations they may also struggle to
actually listen and be able to give the
Strategic advice or ask the right
questions so there is a little bit of
that Nuance there if you can get really
good at the ability of asking questions
of people when you're coaching them you
will get a lot better at being able to
guide them that way and we have
trainings in our in our coaching program
where we help you on how to coach people
how to ask the right questions and how
to listen actively better to be able to
give better advice to people this is a
big methodology that I use is I pay
attention to
all the people that come into our space
that listen to our podcasts that join
our coaching programs what are they
dealing with and I can tell you this one
thing right here
trying to do all the right things
is what stops people from success
it's the interpretation of how they
of what they believe the right things
are
so they're they're trying to do all the
right things they might even be doing
all the right things
but there's like one little piece that
they interpreted off
and oftentimes finding that
interpretation that's the process that
sometimes takes 6 12 18 24 months to get
there and it can feel like you're just
banging your head against the wall and
nothing is being successful this is why
most people walk away from success when
they're just three feet away from gold
when they're just three feet away from
finally striking it rich in their
business they walk away
and this is why
when we really boil it down
the obstacle what seems to be stopping
us what seems to be blocking us the
resistance that we run up against is
actually a direct indicator of the path
that we're meant to go down
and so you might be saying okay well
going down that path would mean that I
do something wrong
or what I thought was wrong previously
there are things I do today in my
business that I previously thought were
wrong
and and not morally wrong or anything
like that but just I thought the best
practice wise
doing those things weren't the right
thing to do and now today I'm doing the
things that are the right things to do
and we're successful and so what you
might be saying wait a sec Jeremiah you
just said you're doing all the right
things and now you're successful I'm
trying to do all the right things and
I'm not successful what's the difference
here you just said the biggest problem
is people are trying to do all the right
things now you're contradicting yourself
no we're not okay
because it's all based on what we
perceive and believe the right things to
do are and you're not really going to
discover in your unique business
what those right things are without
experimentation
okay and so having an experimentation
mindset like a child being willing to
test things out try things out being
willing to fail being willing to see
things not work out being willing to
make a mess
fall flat on your face and fail
and being okay with it see that okay
that
is the line most people are unwilling to
cross they're too afraid of consequences
they're too afraid of what might happen
if
the negative consequences of me doing
the quote unquote wrong thing and
they're not willing to test out an
experiment just to see what happens and
sadly oftentimes because of this they
end up repeating the pattern of actually
doing all the wrong things repeatedly
while simultaneously believing that they
are all the right things and they feel
agitated and disappointed and frustrated
because I'm doing all the right things
and nothing seems to be working
I get it I totally get it and this isn't
to judge or to to put you down if that's
you you might be be feeling a little
exposed here by what I'm saying what I
want to say is you want to give yourself
Grace you want to give yourself
compassion you want to realize you've
been you've been doing your best and so
that's great start there because that's
a great place to start
the more you love yourself the more
opportunity you're going to have to
reach your goals
but here's what I want to tell you
when's the last time that you had a
vision for where you're going in your
life
when's the last time you gave yourself
an opportunity to visualize the future
that you want
you might be saying well that's woo crap
no it's not
because
when we head in the direction of our
vision instead of
trying to do all the right things see
in the direction that you go towards
your vision
there may be some actions that you
have judged as I don't want to do that
but it'll get me to my vision that you
might literally have to do
you might literally have to do
the very thing that you've been trying
to avoid to do at the beginning stages
of your business see I see this happen
often here's a great example A lot of
people want the dream of Evergreen
when it comes to their offers and their
their coaching and getting clients the
dream of Evergreen right
but they don't realize to get to the
dream of Evergreen you actually have to
do a live presentation and you might
have to do the live presentation a few
times over
and it might take more effort and energy
than you wanted to put into it
you might say the returns aren't what I
expected
over time
those returns as you stay consistent
start to increase and listen the very
best way to grow a coaching business
right now is by doing live virtual
events
where we end up talking and
communicating with our potential Target
customer
and we do a sales pitch to sell them on
our programs it's the very best way to
get clients it's the very best way to
grow your email list
and I meet a lot of people they're
trying to do everything but that
to grow their coaching business
and then wondering why they're
struggling well because
that formula is the very best formula to
be able to be successful but you might
fail at it your first couple of times
out nobody might show up
nobody might buy it from you and so
that's where we got to optimize we got a
tweak we got to adjust we got to look at
okay how do we make this better how do
we improve our sales pitch how do we
improve our customer acquisition process
we've done this in our business in the
last month
we've lowered our ad spend by 50 while
increasing the output of how many leads
we're getting by 50 we've almost pretty
much doubled our results while cutting
our budget in half it's incredible and
we've actually done that between 15 and
25 percent increase every single month
for the last year
optimizing our campaign making being
able to squeeze more profits out of the
same activity
and so by doing that that allows us to
be able to automate things to be able to
move things into Evergreen to be able to
to to run a recording that we already
know is a proven sales pitch and to be
able to bring in clients but it didn't
start that way okay
you know I see so many people they're
waiting until things in their life go
how they want them to and they become so
attached to the version of their future
that they wanted
that they miss out
on being able to take advantage of the
opportunities that present itself you
know chat gbt is a great example of this
it only has enough information up to
2021 2021 is the knowledge cutoff of
chat GPT there are people right now that
refuse to use chat GPT because it's
outdated
the 2021. when there are plenty of
opportunities we use it every single day
I used it to come up with what I wanted
to talk about today in this podcast
episode I used it 30 other times a day
to help come up with emails and
marketing and and Facebook ads and a
script for my Facebook ads and we show
you how to do that in our coaching
program like half the
stuff that you used to have to manually
do when it comes to copywriting chat gbt
just does it when you give it the right
props super easy super simple saves you
lots of time saves you a lot of energy
that we used to have to do manually
but people will refuse to use it because
oh it's not right I've even heard people
it's the devil you know Satan is inside
of the AI and it's the devil giving you
good information so they refuse to use
it because they think it's actually the
Spirit of
Satan giving them the stuff inside of
chat gbt whatever I think it's kind of
silly
but they will refuse to do what is gonna
make them be successful in their
business because there are beliefs about
lines that they're not willing to cross
if somebody has a line that they're not
willing to cross their business I refuse
to use artificial intelligence to write
copy because I think it's Satan
in this Marketplace they're going to be
left behind by business owners that are
willing to do that
and so that becomes a line that that
person is unwilling the cross that's
preventing them from being successful
and again you know they may be a moral
issue to them at that point
in this Marketplace
um
you're gonna get eaten alive if you're
not using AI to Market your business to
Market your coaching your mentoring your
training and even using it to augment
your training I now use chat GPT has
gotten really good at tuning it to
actually augment my coaching it actually
helps me get better at my coaching it
helps me make better arguments helps me
influence better I have it help me help
you guys understand what I'm talking
about often
very often
I mean my sales pitch is better it's
made everything better in fact
but there are people who won't use it
and they will continue to struggle to
get customers and clients and wonder why
am I struggling when literally the
opportunity is right in front of them to
succeed but they say no to it because
they're doing all the right things and
so understand that the desire to do all
the right things exactly in the
controlled version that we've come up
with in our mind listen you want to head
towards a vision but you want to hold
Loosely to how you reach that vision
if you hold so tightly
to how you reach a specific Vision it
will often Escape you
and so when we can learn to let go
of how we're going to get to the
destination
and we become more fluid in the process
part of it we can start to trust the
process to say okay
maybe I go in this direction and I
previously had avoided out of fear and
worry but now I know okay that's the
right path to go you know nine months
ago
I was very much trying to avoid working
with people that were making under 200
000 a year that were perfectionists that
were struggling with a lot of these
things and so I had to grow over the
last nine months in my confidence to be
able to work with that market now we're
actually working with that market we're
attracting more people from that segment
because a lot of them are really
attracted to me they're really attracted
to what we're doing and they want to
know how to be successful and so there's
a whole segment of the market that I
need to serve but I had to grow in the
skill set to serve that market
see what I'm saying and so it was a line
that I wasn't willing to cross six
months ago now I am and we're actually
starting to our business is scaling
because of it faster
okay and so ultimately you've got to
look at
what are those sacred cows that you said
I am unwilling to cross that line
because I'm trying to do all the right
things
in your business
and what are some of those things that
you've been avoiding because it's been
too hard
to go in that direction
it might just be in fact I I I can say
this with confidence it probably is
the path that you should be going down
the path of
resistance
in this business is often the path
to success and it will start to become
easy it will start to become the path of
least resistance it's actually really
cool once you start to like
get good at doing this and and
Discerning this and understanding it the
path of the most resistance actually
becomes the path of least resistance and
that's where it gets really really fun
really really easy but there is a
transition period where you go through
or it might be scary it might be hard
you might have to do the very things
that you have said I will never do that
I've I'm doing things today that I've
said I will never do that
and yet I'm doing them on a regular
basis and that's how our business is
making the kind of money that we're
making and I'm excited to pass this on
to you and so hopefully this inspires
you listen this is an advanced level
training right here that I've given in
this podcast episode and that's what
this podcast episode list is if you go
through all the previous episodes of
this podcast they are advanced level
trainings that will change your life
change your mind change your business if
you start to apply them I would actually
go in reverse order and kind of listen
to them all backwards personally I would
not start at episode one I would go
backwards and listen through them you'll
get a lot of value and listen if you
want to join our coaching program the
client growth accelerator
get on the waiting list when we open the
doors to it again you'll be the first to
know to jump into that in the meantime
join us for some of the free events that
we have go through the podcast episodes
check out all the YouTube videos that we
do we got lots of content that can help
you succeed
I can't wait to help you become the
millionaire coach that you know you can
be
we'll talk soon everybody grow your life
foreign